Yes, the last way to reset this in that for a different meeting. So now we'll call it over at their regular schedule of me and my own city council from Monday October 2nd 2023-2 proclamation declaring October 15th 2020 3db Kayla Shawn Day Of Kindness
My commotion? Second
Hi
I got a lot of family here and we're going to come down with proclamation,
And he might want us get in this picture.
Then will meet right there from...
He'll tell you all about it because if happens every time
Tags on your follow up
We'll take a look over now
Thank You Brian
You're so...
What do you go on an info?
I think we're going to get a info
We took the shortcut, Brad
We're going to go there if you like, we'll continue
But I mean just got that door Kevin can show where it's at
Number 3 public input runs into personal purchases
First of all he has lowest Jones
Miss Jones
She is coming this night about a condemned home
Next the order on 24k southeast
Good evening gentlemen
I understand, i'm going to have three minutes
To talk fast
Okay
Good
I've got a concern
A complete and aggravation of the dilapidated houses
Condemned houses on K Street south east
One right next door to me
And it's in bad shape
And I am tired of the mice and rats
Taking up housekeeping at my house
Last week, came out from underneath that house
I'm going to snake
She killed it
Now she was ready for taking a trip
But always does
That's not her way
My dumpster
Last Saturday we could go Saturday
I was checking my glue pads
Blue boards for the mice
And i opened up to kitchen cabinet
Low and behold laying on that blue pad
Was a copper head
Copperhead
This is time of year
For them re-born
My daughter, visit in
In this snake out here
She got it out
And i put it in two trash bags
And tied up and threw them at the dumpster
The houses full of tires, car tyres
There have been sleepless homeless people sleeping
To me its a total fire hazard
It's a nuisance
Celd enforcer told to you that
I thought David walked her own house
On K Street
But on an important day
He sold him
So i don't know how anybody is supposed to get home
Of the owner
They can go decor and
Get permission or whatever they do
To have that house tore down
And he also owns one in
The next block, south of me
Half a vid on this ground
It's really concerned
With homeless people coming
Going all the critters come into visit
And this is me
I'm about up to here
It's been a long time
Now, Christy from when she called me last week
She said there had not be electricity in that house
Since 2014
The neighbors
Here say it was 07
When the flood hit
But apparently
Hasn't been empty since then
If There were electricity and on the 14th
I just wanted to let you know
That these dilapidated houses
Especially the one next door
Me needs To come down
You passed me three minutes
As if your 3 mins is up
We appreciate it
And we're going follow-up on for ya
Appreciate, thank y'all
Thankyou
Martin Lively
Good evening
One in two
I know many of you were already aware
It's going to be an amazing conference
This is the 25th year
There have been back there
And it was in the 40th anniversary
The top three two months
We'll go ahead and visit
We're gonna
Have a presentation from this city
About flooding updates
Really appreciate that
It starts on Tuesday
And that's really important to share
That with the communities
We appreciate it
I just want a highlight of couple
Things we have copies
Of The Agenda
On Tuesday
About flooding
We're gonna
Have a panel
In the hunt here, floodplain
Have completed
We're gonna talk about a few minutes
And they are going to
Talk their experiences
About the process of what
They've been through
I encourage you listen
That will be after
The city, my name is presentation
On Wednesday
Whence's got lot
A part of this date from
From EPA
And they're really notable
First, we'll learn about
Other parts of Superfund
Restoration
We hear a lot
About remediation
The top three trusty council has been hard at work
Developing some specific restoration plans
They are ready to begin
They're gonna talk about that
On Wednesday
In a separate presentation
Myo high school graduate, Tammy Diary
And known of whom
Normally with any other year
Are going to have the implementation
Of an Indigenous youth
A apprenticeship program
Part-of The Restoration Board
We are really critical, keystone species in our watershed
And they're going to be trying
To bring these muscles back
Which hopefully will begin
Bring Back so many other species
That we have lost
Or that, don't happen to a lot of them
So it's very exciting
We are also quite here presentation for Rebecca Stevens
He has worked at the Kurtlein site
But her heel superfunds
She is coming out and talk about what
They've done
She's going to be a part of the few other sites like ours
So I encourage you listen
That, i know my time is about up
And just encourage all
To come and we'll have me
Intertain any questions if he looked at the agenda
You want her better
Thankyou
Thanks for your attention
Yes
Very excited
Yeah, the...
The conference will be important
But before that happens
Coming just this week
We'll have a set of meetings in Pacific Center
On Thursday afternoon
And what we're doing is meeting with people
Who has completed
To give them results
on What Weeks Found
How many people want to buy out
How many people have been flooded
What did it cost them
We want to give back the neighbourhood
People what we've learned and
And then
Will do a series of meetings
To o'clock
For O'clock
In six o' clock
You will welcome to attend
Some are experienced flooding
People that have experienced
But we want to give people
Completed the survey first
Debts it seeing
The results
So what would be doing there afternoon
Anyway possible you can encourage
Not only come
To those meetings
but also
Complete their flood survey
That not done yet
They could still do an online at
Lead Agency website
And we can do it over the phone
Or will come knock on your door again
But
On Tuesday as Martin was
We'll talk about flooding
To this morning
It would be an important meeting
One of biggest things happening
Wednesday is
The rest
Of
Our
We want to tell you what all
Our region's six
Missed doing for us
I've a year going
And we have been
Doing
They had not done
He was head of
Superfund
Retired and now he is trying
To come back
Give
That
We encourage you to help
A spill the ball room up with people
From here
Don't know these facts
How many of us knocked on doors
Did not
No
Our floods were manned
Although we've done the town halls
They have been excellent
Not everybody has gotten that story yet
We've been working on the community
And we have also
The rest of our story here
I want to ask Dusty
To come and over
Tell a little bit about
When do you say that?
Can't speak for us
Wednesday morning
He will be let me check
You're going to hear the history of
Tark Creek
The Pawpock Creek
And Widenle Creek
How many times they've been moved over
Over
In which way
They went and what happened
Then next
We'll follow that
This list
I would imagine it
It'd be about 930
Yeah
Thank you
4 times this
Most of the proof